All right, I want to talk about lead
generation through ads. And I'm not
going to show you the ads manager
necessarily, what ads to set up or
things like that. I have an upcoming
class you can check out on my website.
We should have the link below soon, not
right now today. It might be ready at
the time of this recording, but you can
find it Instagram ads playbook where I
show you step by step how to set up your
Instagram ads, the right ways to do it.
What I want to talk about is the
strategy that we're seeing when it comes
to pricing and lead generation. For the
longest time, we were running webinars
and free challenges to get people to
sign up as leads for our business to
find people that are out there to become
our customers. And so that has changed.
That whole landscape in business has
changed of free lead generation. In
fact,
100 people could be better than 1,000
people. Let me explain this. If I
generate a thousand leads, which by the
way, our strategies that I teach for
lead generation, I could generate you
10,000 leads in a week. I've done it
before. I I did it a couple months ago.
Um, but if these are free leads, right,
when I say free, it's not that they're
free to you, but they cost you money.
You run ads and these are to a free
offer. The quality of these leads now is
poop. It's just a flaming pile of
garbage. Instead, what we're looking for
is we're looking for buyer leads. So,
we're looking for people who are willing
to spend between5 to $10 with you.
Okay? So, let me explain kind of how
this all works. You could do a $5 price
point, you can do a $7 price point, you
could do a $10 price point. Previously,
we would run webinars, we would run
challenges, and they would be free. And
we would just get hundreds of I mean I
remember I would get on every week I get
like 500 to a thousand people to join me
for a webinar. Um easy. It's not hard to
do when you know how to do it. When you
know how to create the right offers and
do all that. That's what I mentor people
on how to do in my wealthy coach academy
program. Here's what's happened though
is the quality of those people. They're
not converting
into
sales for our business. Because again,
if I'm spending money to get these
leads, let's say I'm spending $5 to get
a per person to get a,000 people, that's
going to be $5,000 spent. So now I need
to make at least $5,000
up here in sales. Okay, pretty decent
math. Problem is these thousand people
aren't converting.
Why? That's how business was worked for
the longest time.
It's changed. And what's changed is now
we would rather get a hundred people
or even a thousand people in fact that
are paying us money. And here's the
beauty of it.
To get one person to spend $5 with me or
$10 with me on a on a webinar,
it only cost me about5 to$10 per person
in the ad spend. So, I'm just I'm just
going to do some basic math with you
here.
$5 a person to spend five bucks.
Cost me $5. They give me five bucks. So,
my net average is zero. So, at the end
of the day, it's either costing me zero
to get a hundred or 500 or a,000 people.
Last last week, we got over 609 people
as customers paying us $5 for an offer.
We bumped the price up to 10 bucks. And
guess what? Just as many people started
buying it and and the $10 ended up
costing us 10 bucks. There's a there's a
science behind this. I'll tell you a
little bit about that in a second. But
it cost us nothing
to get those people to be able to
get on our email list and give them a
presentation. And because they spent a
little bit of money instead of being
free,
20 to 30% of them converted into our
paid offer.
So
the like this the math here of all these
free leads because you got a free offer
that's out there doesn't work anymore.
Now we want to take what we were doing
in our free offers. Here's all you do
and you slap a price tag on it. Okay?
And and that's what we're doing. We're
we're no longer like YouTube videos like
like you're like well not everybody can
afford everybody can afford five bucks.
Come on. Literally, you can afford five
bucks. I got I got a $5 offer in the
description of this video. Hopefully, I
think we just finished it at the time of
this recording. It's It's a weird thing
where like you finished the offer, is it
ready to go yet? Is it tested? All that.
It'll be ready to go by the time this
video is up. Okay. You can find it
below. My own version of this. You can
go through it. I like to do where I even
throw a money back guarantee in there
and bonuses and all kinds of crazy stuff
just to make people say, "Listen, five
bucks is like it's a steal. I'm stealing
this from you, Jeremiah." So, anyways,
it costs nothing to get qualified people
in front of you to then make a
presentation to into whatever your paid
program is. And that math checks out
really well because you can scale this
See, why were we not doing this before?
Well, here's the problem. I'm going to
take you back, give you a little history
lesson. Two years ago, even a year ago,
three years ago, when we were trying to
run ads to5 and $10 offers, it was
costing us like 20 to $50
to get people to sign up. And so, free
leads were just as profitable. Now,
it's costing us the same to get people
to sign up for these paid offers.
even if it costs double, it's worth it.
And then you sell your paid offer. So
the idea is to make your ads work. And
that's what my latest class is on. It's
the Instagram ads playbook.
But to make your ads work, you want your
offer to be this lowcost, low ticket
instead of a free lead magnet.
You don't want want to go out there.
Okay, let me explain this. You don't
want to go out there marketing a $10,000
program or a $20,000 program or a $5,000
or even a $2,000 program just right out
the gate with an ad. So, you need some
way to lead people into it. You don't
need to do DMs or cold calls or anything
like that. And that's why the webinar
model works so well is you can put it on
autopilot and you don't need to be there
24/7 to do it. But
when nobody's registering or upselling
from these free offers, you start to
question, okay, is this is this model
working? Well, it it wasn't working, at
least profitably, like we used to get.
And so now this new model right here is
working really well
because we're charging a little bit of
money. And I and I'll throw some urgency
into it. you know, I give people, they
pay me five bucks, they got three days
to watch the training, you know, um they
got if I'm gonna make an offer, there's
three days. I like that kind of 72-hour
time limit for urgency of action that
the people need to take.
And so when you kind of bundle that all
together, you throw in some bonuses, you
throw in um you know, some free courses,
maybe you got an AI tool that you can
offer people. Hint, hint, wink, wink.
That's kind of what we've added into one
of our big offers.
All of this
makes it irresistible for people to sign
up on the back end and you're going to
get a higher quality of person on the
front end. And so I'm telling you, if
you're a coach, if you're a mentor, if
you're a trainer,
your front-end marketing,
like if you're a service provider, I
think there's a value of doing free,
right? Because you get to demonstrate
your service.
But if you're not selling necessarily a
service,
charging a little bit of money for that
information,
giving people a quick win, something
they can learn from. I mean, you could
tell from a video like this, I give wins
all the time to people, tons of
information,
that converts and that produces the
sales that you're looking for. All
right? And that'll make your ads work
better because you're going to be able
to pay for your ad spend. Those are
actually going to be qualified people
that are going to buy from you on the
back end. It's all going to work out
much better. Listen, check out that
training in the description and check
out my Wealthy Coach Academy program
when we open the doors to it. Love to
see you in there. Love to work with you.
Talk soon.